Trisha

Phone: +919870636306

Address: Mathura,India

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/trishat1999

Email: trisha13021999@gmail.com

Summary

A cloud computing professional with 2.5+ years of experience using Microsoft Azure. A strong knowledge of Cloud platform and Azure DevOps, good in working with infrastructure as a code tools such as Terraform, Golang, PowerShell and ARM templates. Experienced in analyzing, designing, developing, maintaining the services.

EXPERIENCE

Neudesic, An IBM Company

August 2020 - Current

DevOps Engineer

- Working as DevOps Specialist and consulting multiple clients on their infrastructure and software development & their deployment
- Day-to-day activities: Developing end-to-end CI/CD Pipelines, Automating client's infrastructure, Maintaining cloud infrastructures
- · Managing Azure Repository, Master, and feature branches, Pull requests, Branch policies
- Implementing YAML pipeline stages for different environments, Development, QA, Production
- Creating and testing Azure resources using Terraform, Raising PRs and work on new features & update the Terraform code for new versions
- Technologies: Microsoft Azure, Terraform, Golang, PowerShell

Capgemini December 2020 - August 2022

PaaS Support Team

- Setting up PaaS Environment in Azure based on requirements
- Implementing the Governance using Azure Management Group, Policies, and IAM
- Migrating the resource groups across different subscriptions
- Managing Identity and access management across different subscriptions, Azure resource group and resource
- Create and manage Security groups in Azure AD and User management
- Implementing SSO for Enterprise Application and Access Management Setup conditional access policies based on the request Service Now Integration with Azure AD and configuring auto-provisioning users
- Adding custom roles to App registration
- Creating and managing user accounts
- Building and managing the Azure Storage Accounts, Generating the SAS keys for storage accounts Managing Power BI pro licenses and Workspaces.
- Migrating Power BI standard Workspace to premium capacity Workspace
- Fetching information from Azure using PowerShell
- Taking initiatives from remediation and cost perspective. Cost Management in Azure
- Deploying Resources using Azure
- Managing Identity and access management across different Azure resource group and resources Setting up alerting mechanisms and Monitoring Azure Infrastructure

EDUCATION

Arya College of Engineering And IT

August 2016 - August 2020

Bachelor of Technology - Electronics And Communication

SKILLS

- Administration: Windows, Linux, Networking
- Cloud Platforms: Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- Infrastructure Automation Tools: Terraform, Golang, PowerShell, Python, YAML, DevOps Tools
- DevOps Tools: Git, Azure DevOps (ADO), Packer, SonarQube

PROJECTS

Infrastructure Testing Automation Accelerator

February 2023-Present

- 1. This project involves creating and automating Terratest test cases for Infrastructure as Code written with Terraform
- 2. Role: DevOps Engineer
- 3. Responsibilities: Creation and Automation of Terratest tests for IaC written with Terraform

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Certified Azure Fundamentals

Microsoft

Microsoft Certified Azure Administrator Associate

Microsoft

LANGUAGES

English (Professional), Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Declaration: I hereby declare that all the facts mentioned above are accurate, and I take full responsibility for their accuracy.

Trisha